[
    {
        "question": "Savitri may keep me waiting",
        "words": {
          "4": "Savitri",
          "1": "waited",
          "3": "I",
          "2": "keeping",
          "5": "by",
          "6": "to",
          "7": "kept",
          "8": "may",
          "9": "waiting",
          "10": "be"
        },
        "answers":[[3,8,10,7,9,5,4]]
    },
    {
        "question": "It looks nice that they had painted the house blue",
        "words": {
          "4": "them",
          "1": "painted",
          "3": "been",
          "2": "nice",
          "5": "the",
          "6": "it",
          "7": "that",
          "8": "by",
          "9": "is",
          "10": "house",
          "11": "blue",
          "12": "looks",
          "13": "had"
        },
        "answers":[[6,12,2,7,5,10,13,3,1,11,8,4]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Bring it home",
        "words": {
          "4": "home",
          "1": "be",
          "3": "let",
          "2": "requested",
          "5": "are",
          "6": "brought",
          "7": "asked",
          "8": "it",
          "9": "to",
          "10": "you"
        },
        "answers":[[3,8,1,6,4]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Do it at once",
        "words": {
          "4": "once",
          "1": "let",
          "3": "be",
          "2": "ordered",
          "5": "done",
          "6": "are",
          "7": "requested",
          "8": "at",
          "9": "it",
          "10": "do",
          "11": "you",
          "12": "to"
        },
        "answers":[[1,9,3,5,8,4]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Do not insult the weak",
        "words": {
          "4": "insult",
          "1": "weak",
          "3": "be",
          "2": "let",
          "5": "requested",
          "6": "not",
          "7": "are",
          "8": "insulted",
          "9": "the",
          "10": "to",
          "11": "you"
        },
        "answers":[[2,6,9,1,3,8]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Do not beat the dog",
        "words": {
          "4": "dog",
          "1": "not",
          "3": "you",
          "2": "to",
          "5": "let",
          "6": "asked",
          "7": "be",
          "8": "are",
          "9": "beaten",
          "10": "the"
        },
        "answers":[[5,10,4,1,7,9]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Let me do it",
        "words": {
          "4": "me",
          "1": "you",
          "3": "let",
          "2": "be",
          "5": "are",
          "6": "it",
          "7": "done",
          "8": "requested",
          "9": "by",
          "10": "to"
        },
        "answers":[[3,6,2,7,9,4]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Let Gopal marry Dipanwita",
        "words": {
          "4": "Gopal",
          "1": "be",
          "3": "by",
          "2": "let",
          "5": "to",
          "6": "married",
          "7": "Dipanwita"
        },
        "answers":[[2,7,1,6,3,4]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Get out",
        "words": {
          "4": "you",
          "1": "out",
          "3": "to",
          "2": "are",
          "5": "be",
          "6": "being",
          "7": "get",
          "8": "ordered",
          "9": "got"
        },
        "answers":[[4,2,8,3,7,1]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Work hard",
        "words": {
          "4": "advised",
          "1": "do",
          "3": "you",
          "2": "hard",
          "5": "to",
          "6": "being",
          "7": "are",
          "8": "work",
          "9": "be"
        },
        "answers":[[3,7,4,5,8,2]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Please give me some money",
        "words": {
          "4": "you",
          "1": "some",
          "3": "to",
          "2": "me",
          "5": "requested",
          "6": "are",
          "7": "give",
          "8": "money",
          "9": "asked"
        },
        "answers":[[4,6,5,3,7,2,1,8]]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kindly do this work",
        "words": {
          "4": "requested",
          "1": "do",
          "3": "work",
          "2": "you",
          "5": "this",
          "6": "are",
          "7": "to",
          "8": "done",
          "9": "let",
          "10": "be"
        },
        "answers":[[2,6,4,7,1,5,3]]
    }
]